An ordinary everyday, a clear and cloudless Sunday
何気のない日々 晴れた日曜日
This normal ordinariness is so boring
普通ばっかの日常 つまんないよ
I spotted a white rabbit running before my eyes
目の前走ってく白いうさぎ見つけた
Let’s chase its round, little bristling tail
揺れる小さな丸いしっぽ追ってみよう
Hey, where on earth am I?
ねぇここはいったいどこなの？
It’s a brilliant world as vivid as paint
絵の具のような鮮やかな世界
Ah, what a lovely song
あぁ心地いい歌 聞こえてきて
I start singing along before thinking twice
思わず一緒に歌っていたよ
It’s a world of glittering fantasy
きらめいてるファンタジ — なワ — ルド
There’s no time to feel bored
退屈さは感じる暇もない
It’s like peeking into a picture book
絵本の中覗いてるような
What are you in the mood to play next?
気分でなにして次は遊ぼう
Heart, diamond,
ハ — トもダイヤも
spade, and clover, let’s all play together!
スペ — ドもクロ — バ — も御一緒に！
We ate some small, sweet cookies and grew big
小さな甘いクッキ — 食べて大きくなった
“Sorry!” Looks like I caused trouble for you again
「ごめんね！」また困らせちゃったみたい
In this secret world that adults don’t understand,
大人には分かんない秘密の世界で
I frolic around, go wild, and do as I please
好き放題はしゃいではめ外す
I can’t find my way back home anymore
もう帰り道もわからない
I’m just a crybaby inside a deep forest
深い森で泣き虫な私
Ah, that mischievous cat told me
あぁ いたずらな猫は言った
that "happiness is just the little things”
「幸せはほんの些細なこと」って
It’s a story so ridiculous it just can’t be real
ありえないくらいおかしなスト — リ —
Did my plain, familiar scenery disappear?
見慣れていた景色は消えたの？
It’s something I wished for ever since I was little
幼い頃から願ってた夢
But now that it’s come true, it feels kind of lonely
叶ったのになぜか淋しいよ
Who is it that’s there smiling suspiciously with red eyes?
紅い瞳で怪しく微笑んだのは誰？
Why do strange things happen in succession wherever I go?
ホントそろそろ帰らないと
It's indeed about time to go home
みんな心配しちゃうからね
Everyone would worry about me
でも、どっち行けばいいの？
Well, it's up to you, isn't it?
まあ、それはキミ次第なんじゃない？
Your answer does not make sense
え〜！それじゃ答えになってない
If you don't know which way you should go,
どっち行きたいか分かんないなら
there is not a big difference whichever you go
どっちの道へ行ったって、たいした違いはないよ
But there is a place I want to go
それでも私にはいきたい場所があるの
I want to go home even if I don't know the way
道が分からなくても、帰りたいの
Please tell me
教えて
I don't know
知らん
For goodness' sake please tell me
だから教えて
Dunno
え〜、知らん
Tell me!
教えろ〜
There’s a voice calling for me  on the other side of the door
わたし呼ぶ声 扉の向こう側から
It’s a glittering fantasy world
きらめいてるファンタジ — なワ — ルド
Curious incidents and lots of different encounters
不思議な事件 沢山の出会いも
But I gaze around at my same old room, painted orange
オレンジ色に染まったいつもの部屋
with a little bit of relief
少しほっとした気分で眺めた
As I stretch and yawn, I spot a patch of mud left on my foot
あくびしながら足に残る泥を見つけて
and whisper “thank you” with a smile
そっとありがとうって微笑んだ